stylefrizz.com 2019-04-28

# Privacy Policy - StyleFrizz

Thank you for visiting _Stylefrizz_. The information we collect here (your personally identifiable information – name, e-mail address) enable us to provide you with the type of service you require (comments or subscriptions) and communicate with you (newsletters or contact).

If you choose to send information for publication (“contact form”), your name, screen name and/or any other information you wanted to appear on the website may be published. 

Some of our pages may contain links to other websites, non-related to _Stylefrizz_. Their privacy policy may be different than ours and as such you should read their privacy notices in order to keep your personal information safe. 

To ease your navigation, each time your return to _Stylefrizz_ , a cookies system can help you recognize your name and your e-mail. That’s possible only if your “cookies” are enabled. Cookies are pieces of information stored by a website on your computer. If you choose to not receive any cookies, you may deactivate the option from your browser’s menu.

We do our best to provide you with the best and the most secure service possible. However, this website’s security may be subject to vulnerability and as such we cannot be held responsible for any security breach.

_Stylefrizz_ is not credited for the images used on the website unless it’s specifically mentioned so. The photographs are usually edited in order to provide you with the best information available. All images and sources are credited.

We also use third party advertisements on stylefrizz.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

DoubleClick DART cookies  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting New York, you may see New York hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting <http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx>

This is a general audience site. If you have any questions about this policy or any other aspect involving _Stylefrizz_ , please [contact](http://stylefrizz.com/contact/) us. 

_Stylefrizz_ reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time notifying the change of privacy statement. This privacy statement and the privacy policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party.
